OKAY, RACH, THAT'S MUFFIN
AND ESPRESSO, $4.50
ROSS, DOUBLE LATTE, $2.75
CHANDLER, COFFEE
AND SCONE, $4.25
AND PHEEBS, HERBAL TEA, $1.25.
SO, ALL TOGETHER, THAT'S $12.75.
THIS COMING FROM THE MAN
WHO COULDN'T SPLIT
OUR $80 PHONE BILL IN HALF.
HI.
HOW MUCH DO I OWE
FOR THE MUFFIN AND LATTE?
THAT'S ON THE HOUSE
COURTESY OF
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
OH, GREAT.
WELL, TELL HIM THANKS.
AND SINCE, UH, JOEY
SEEMS LIKE SUCH A NICE GUY
MAYBE WE COULD
GO ON A DATE SOMETIME.
WELL, HE'S NOT USED
TO WOMEN BEING SO FORWARD
BUT, UH, I COULD
CHECK WITH HIM.
HE SAYS IT'S OKAY.
GREAT. THANKS.
BYE-BYE.
HEY, JOEY, HOW COME
OUR STUFF ISN'T FREE?
IT WILL BE WHEN YOU
LOOK LIKE THAT
IN A TIGHT SKIRT.
THIS IS GREAT. I'M GETTING
MORE DATES THAT EVER.
WAIT A MINUTE.
JOEY, YOU'RE ONLY
GIVING AWAY FREE STUFF
TO THE PRETTY GIRLS?
JOEY, THAT IS
SO GROSS.
HOW ABOUT A SCONE
ON THE HOUSE, BABY?
I'M PRETTY.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO... ♪
HEY, DOES ANYONE
HAVE ANY GUM?
OH, I DO.
HERE, SORRY.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO.
WAIT A SECOND...
( plastic bag rustling )
I KNOW IT'S IN
HERE SOMEWHERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M GOOD, I'M GOOD.
HEY.
HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE AT WORK?
UH, THEY SENT ME HOME.
THEY SAID I CAN'T WORK
IF I'M SICK.
All:
OH!
I'M SORRY YOU'RE SICK.
I'M NOT SICK!
I DON'T GET SICK.
GETTING SICK IS FOR WEAKLINGS.
IT'S FOR PANSIES.
HONEY, NO ONE THINKS
THAT YOU'RE A PANSY.
BUT WE DO THINK
THAT YOU NEED A TISSUE.
I HAVE NOT BEEN SICK
IN OVER THREE YEARS.
( sneezes )
I'M GOING TO GRAB YOU
SOME TISSUE.
I-I DON'T NEED
A TISSUE!
I'M FINE'D!
WHEN YOU PUT A "D"
AT THE END OF "FINE"
YOU'RE NOT FINE.
I'M FINE... 'D.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S
A REALLY HARD WORD TO SAY.
( knocking on door )
YES?
HI. IS RACHEL HERE?
I'M HER SISTER.
OH, MY GOD! JILL!
OH, MY GOD! RACHEL!
HI!
OH, MY GOD!
INTRODUCE US.
WELL, THIS IS CHANDLER.
AND YOU KNOW
MONICA AND ROSS.
AND THAT'S PHOEBE
AND THAT'S JOEY.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
DON'T!
HONEY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
WHICH-WHICH
SISTER IS THIS?
IS THIS THE SPOILED ONE
OR THE ONE THAT BIT HER?
DADDY CUT ME OFF.
NEVER MIND. I GOT IT.
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT I SAID TO HIM?
I SAID, "I'M GOING
TO HIRE A LAWYER
"AND I'M GOING
TO SUE YOU
"AND TAKE
ALL YOUR MONEY
AND THEN I'M GOING
TO CUT YOU OFF!"
WOW, WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE SAID HE WOULDN'T
PAY FOR MY LAWYER.
AND THEN HE TOLD ME
TO COME HERE AND LEARN
ABOUT THE VALUE OF MONEY
FROM THE ONE
DAUGHTER HE'S
ACTUALLY PROUD OF.
( gasps )
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
MY DAD'S PROUD OF ME.
RACH...
OH, YEAH, SORRY.
OKAY, HONEY,
SO WHAT DID YOU DO
THAT MADE DAD
CUT YOU OFF?
OKAY, I BOUGHT A BOAT.
YOU BOUGHT A BOAT?
YEAH, BUT IT WASN'T FOR ME,
IT WAS FOR A FRIEND.
BOY, DID WE MAKE FRIENDS
WITH THE WRONG SISTER.
JILL, HONEY,
I THINK THIS IS
THE BEST THING
THAT COULD HAVE
EVER HAPPENED TO YOU.
YOU'VE NEEDED TO GET OUT
ON YOUR OWN, ANYWAY.
AND, YOU KNOW,
WHEN I DID IT
I-I, AT FIRST
I WAS SCARED,
BUT THEN,
LOOK AT ME NOW.
I AM THE
ONLY DAUGHTER
THAT DAD IS PROUD OF.
OKAY, THIS
IS WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO.
YOU'RE GOING
TO GET A JOB.
TO GET AN APARTMENT.
AND THEN
I'LL HELP YOU
AND YOU CAN
STAY WITH US.
RIGHT, PHEEBS?
OF COURSE, YEAH.
OH, THAT'S SO GREAT.
OKAY, I'M REALLY
GOING TO DO THIS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO THANK YOU GUYS.
OH, I LIKE CARS.
UH, ARE YOU
ALL FINISHED HERE?
YES.
GREAT.
OKAY, HERE ARE
THE TIPS FOR
THIS MORNING.
MM.
JAN GETS $50, $50 FOR ME
AND JOEY OWES
EIGHT DOLLARS.
WHAT?
FOR ALL THE FREE FOOD
YOU GAVE AWAY.
WELL, IF IT'S
FREE FOOD
HOW COME YOU'RE
CHARGING ME FOR IT?
WE DON'T GIVE
ANYTHING AWAY
UNLESS IT'S
SOMEONE'S BIRTHDAY.
OH... WHA-WHAT IF
THEY CAME IN THIRD
IN A MODELING CONTEST?
NO.
HMM...
SORRY.
I JUST HAD THE HARDEST DAY.
SOME OF THESE ARE SO HEAVY.
JILL, HOW DID YOU PAY
FOR ALL THIS?
I THOUGHT YOUR DAD
TOOK AWAY YOUR CREDIT CARD.
OH, PLEASE. I MEMORIZED
THOSE NUMBERS WHEN I WAS 15.
BUT, LOOK AT ALL THE COOL
MAKE-IT-ON-MY-OWN STUFF I GOT.
THIS IS
MY "PLEASE HIRE ME" SWEATER.
AND THESE ARE MY...
"DON'T YOU WANT TO RENT ME
THIS APARTMENT?" PANTS.
I DON'T THINK CHARGING
NEW CLOTHES TO YOUR DAD
QUALIFIES AS MAKING IT
ON YOUR OWN.
OH, MR. SCIENTIST
HAS TO GET ALL TECHNICAL.
SERIOUSLY, I DON'T THINK
RACHEL'S GOING TO THINK
IT'S SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
SO, WHO MADE HER
QUEEN OF THE WORLD?
OH, I WOULD
LOVE THAT JOB.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
HEY.
JILL...
DID YOU SHOP?
NO.
THEY DID.
Both:
YEAH, WE WENT SHOPPING!
YOU WENT SHOPPING?
WHAT? AND THEN YOU
JUST CAME IN HERE
AND PARADED IT
RIGHT UNDER JILL'S NOSE
WHEN YOU KNOW
SHE'S TRYING TO QUIT?
WOW, YOU GUYS, IT'S TERRIBLE.
SORRY, JILL.
SORRY-SORRY, JILL.
SO, WHAT
DID YOU GET?
OH, WELL,
ALL RIGHT
I GOT... THANK YOU, I GOT THIS
"I WANT A JOB" SWEATER.
OH.
AND THEN I GOT,
UH, THESE...
ARE APARTMENT
PANTS.
APARTMENT PANTS?
YEAH, YOU'VE NEVER
HEARD OF THEM?
WELL, NO, OF COURSE,
OF COURSE I'VE HEARD OF THEM.
ROSS, WHAT
DID YOU GET?
HUH?
I GOT THIS... THIS.
A PASHMINA?
YEAH.
I-I LOVE THESE BABIES.
REALLY?
MM.
ROSS, WHAT'S A PASHMINA?
IT'S A RUG.
JILL.
( fake crying and sobbing )
I'M SORRY, RACHEL.
OH, COME ON.
YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S GOING TO WORK ON ME?
I INVENTED THAT.
RIGHT.
BUT I AM SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S OKAY.
ONE LITTLE SETBACK
IS OKAY.
BUT JUST DON'T LET IT
HAPPEN AGAIN, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
NOW, SINCE DADDY
PAID FOR ALL
THIS STUFF
I SHOULD TAKE IT ALL AWAY
BUT I'M JUST GOING TO TAKE...
THE-THE PASHMINA.
AND THE-AND THE, UH, PANTS.
AND, YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M JUST
GOING TO TAKE IT ALL AWAY
'CAUSE THAT WAY, YOU'LL JUST
REALLY LEARN THE LESSON, OKAY?
ALL RIGHTY.
WELL, I'M GOING
TO RUN A COUPLE OF ERRANDS
AND I WILL SEE YOU AT DINNER.
( sighs )
SHE TOOK ALL
MY STUFF.
YEAH, EVERYTHING BUT...
THE LITTLE BLUE ONE.
( gasps )
OH! THAT'S
THE BEST ONE!
OH, MY GOD!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
WELL, HEY...
OH, MY GOSH,
THAT WAS SO LAME.
LIKE A PASHMINA
COULD BE A RUG.
OH, YEAH, WELL,
HOW ABOUT YOU WITH
"OH, I'M SORRY..."
OH, SHUT UP! IT
WASN'T LIKE
THAT AT ALL.
WHAT ABOUT- WHAT ABOUT
WHAT I SAID
ABOUT THE APARTMENT PANTS?
HOW DUMB WAS I? HA!
WERE YOU THIS CUTE
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
OH, STOP.
NO, YOU STOP.
YOU STOP.
OKAY, OKAY,
WHY DON'T
I SIT HERE
AND THEN YOU'LL
BOTH STOP IT.
OKAY, SO WHAT
DO YOU WANT TO DO?
LET'S DO SOMETHING CRAZY!
I KNOW. LET'S REST
AND DRINK LOTS OF FLUIDS.
OKAY, I'LL REST, BUT, YOU KNOW,
IF I'M GOING TO BED
THEN YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
( sniffs )
SEE, THAT WOULD BE
IMPOSSIBLE TO RESIST
IF YOU WEREN'T ALL DRIPPY HERE.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU DON'T
WANT TO GET WITH THIS?
YEAH, I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD SAY THAT
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE HEALTHY.
OH, COME ON.
( coughing )
DON'T TAKE THIS
PERSONALLY, OKAY.
IT'S JUST THAT I JUST CAN'T
HAVE SEX WITH A SICK PERSON.
I'M WITH YOU, CHANDLER.
I MEAN, I CAN'T HAVE SEX
WITH A SICK PERSON, EITHER.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
BUT I'M NOT SICK.
LET ME PROVE IT TO YOU.
WE ARE TWO HEALTHY PEOPLE
AT THE PRIBE OF LIBE.
SEE, THAT'S THE THING.
I WOULD LIKE TO STAY
IN THE PRAHM-UB-LABH.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
UM... I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD MAYBE KNOW.
WELL, IT BETTER NOT BE
ABOUT THE APARTMENT PANTS
BECAUSE I JUST PITCHED THE IDEA
TO MY BOSS AT RALPH LAUREN
AND SHE LOVED IT.
OH, NO, NO, IT'S JUST...
I WAS, UM, I WAS
WITH ROSS AND JILL
AFTER YOU LEFT AND, UM,
I'M PRETTY SURE
I SAW A LITTLE SPARK
BETWEEN THEM.
WHAT?
YEAH, I MEAN IT'S
PROBABLY NOTHING
BUT I JUST WANTED TO WARN YOU
THAT THERE MIGHT BE
SOMETHING THERE.
WITH ROSS AND JILL?
YEAH.
WITH ROSS AND MY SISTER?
WITH MY SISTER, JILL,
AND MY EX-BOYFRIEND, ROSS?
YEAH.
OH, THERE IS NO WAY.
OKAY, THEN.
OH, MY GOD!
I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT!
I DON'T
REALLY LIKE IT
WHEN ROSS GOES OUT
WITH ANYONE
BUT MY SISTER?!
ISN'T THAT LIKE INCEST
OR SOMETHING?
OH, MY GOD
AND THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE SEX.
OH, NO, AND WHAT
IF HE MARRIES HER, TOO?
OH, THIS IS
JUST TERRIBLE.
THIS IS JUST TERRIBLE.
AND I CAN'T STOP IT.
I DON'T OWN ROSS, YOU KNOW
AND JILL, SHE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO DO WHATEVER IT IS
THAT SHE WANTS TO DO.
AND, OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
ROSS IS MARRYING
MY LITTLE SISTER.
OH, MY GOD. THIS IS
JUST THE WORST THING
THAT COULD HAVE EVER
HAPPENED TO ME.
BUT GREAT NEWS
ABOUT THE APARTMENT PANTS, HUH?
THAT'LL BE $3.85.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YESTERDAY YOU SAID
I WAS TOO PRETTY
TO PAY FOR STUFF.
IT'S JUST I CAN'T
BECAUSE MY MANAGER SAID THAT...
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY DEAR ANNIE... ♪
AMY.
♪ AMY ♪
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
HEY, THAT'S WEIRD.
TODAY'S MY BIRTHDAY, TOO.
YEAH, NOT IN HERE IT ISN'T.
SORRY I'M LATE.
WHAT'S UP?
OH, HI.
UH, YOU KNOW, I JUST
WANTED TO SEE
IF THERE WERE ANY LEADS
ON THE OLD JOB FRONT.
OH, NO, BUT I JUST WALKED PAST
THREE SALES AND I DIDN'T GO IN.
HOW STRONG AM I?
OH...
THAT IS GREAT.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHO DOESN'T
HAVE TO JOB HUNT?
ROSS.
HE WORKS AT THE UNIVERSITY.
YEAH.
SO YOU KNOW THAT.
YOU GUYS TALKED ABOUT THAT.
SO YOU GET ALONG. SO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO GO OUT?
ME GO OUT WITH ROSS?
NO.
GOD, NO!
WHAT WOULD MAKE
YOU THINK THAT?
IT'S JUST... PHOEBE...
SAID SHE, YOU KNOW
THOUGHT SHE SAW SOMETHING
BETWEEN YOU GUYS.
NO.
I MEAN, HE'S NICE.
HE'S THE KIND OF GUY
YOU'RE FRIENDS WITH
BUT HE'S NOT THE KIND
OF GUY YOU DATE.
I MEAN, HE'S THE KIND
OF GUY YOU DATE
'CAUSE YOU DID, BUT...
ME...
NOT SO MUCH.
UM, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN, IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG WITH ROSS?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
HE'S JUST...
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, HE'S JUST
A LITTLE... BOOKISH.
ARE YOU SAYING
HE'S A GEEK?
YOU THINK SO, TOO?
NO. NO, ROSS
IS NOT A GEEK.
FINE.
THEN LET'S JUST SAY
HE'S NOT MY TYPE.
HANDSOME IS NOT YOUR TYPE?
SMART, KIND, GOOD KISSER?
WHAT? THOSE THINGS
AREN'T ON YOUR LIST?
ROSS IS A GREAT GUY.
YOU WOULD BE LUCKY
TO BE WITH HIM.
WELL, OKAY, IF IT
MEANS THAT MUCH TO YOU
THEN I'LL JUST
ASK HIM OUT.
OH, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
I WAS JUST TRYING...
YOU KNOW WHAT, RACHEL.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, HE HAS
BEEN REALLY NICE TO ME.
YEAH, BUT HE'S
NOT YOUR TYPE.
YEAH, BUT MAYBE
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
YOU KNOW, I'M DOING
ALL THESE DIFFERENT
SORTS OF THINGS.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST
TRY DATING A GEEK, TOO.
YEAH, BUT YOU
DON'T WANT TO TRY
TOO MUCH, TOO FAST.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN
YOU DO REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE LITTLE GIRL
WHO TRIED TOO MUCH
TOO FAST, DON'T YOU?
WHAT?
SHE-SHE DIED, JILL.
Monica:
CHANDLER!
OH, WHAT IS IT, HONEY?
YOU NEED SOME TEA?
SOME SOUP?
OH, OH, OH!
CALLING DR. BING...
DR. BING, TO THE BED.
OH, GEEZ, HONEY,
I THOUGHT...
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE ASLEEP.
HOW CAN I BE ASLEEP
KNOWING THAT YOU WERE
IN THE NEXT ROOM?
I WAS ASLEEP.
( shivering )
OH, NO, NO, NO, HONEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S SEXY?
LAYERS.
LAYERS ARE SEXY...
AND BLANKETS ARE SEXY
AND, OH, HOT WATER BOTTLES
ARE SEXY.
COME ON, GET INTO BED.
I WANT TO PROVE
THAT I'M NOT SICK.
I WANT TO MAKE YOU FEEL...
AS GOOD AS I FEEL.
( sneezing )
WOULD YOU PLEASE GET SOME REST?
I'M FINE...
( coughing )
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU. ♪
YOU'RE PAYING FOR THAT.
WHAT? NO, NO,
IT'S HER BIRTHDAY.
YOU'VE SUNG
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO 20 DIFFERENT
WOMEN TODAY.
BUT IT REALLY...
YOU ARE
NO LONGER AUTHORIZED
TO DISTRIBUTE
BIRTHDAY MUFFINS.
DAMN IT!
RACH.
HI.
DID YOU TELL YOUR SISTER
TO ASK ME OUT?
WELL, YEAH...
OH, WOW!
I MEAN, WOW!
I THINK SHE'S CUTE
BUT I NEVER
WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
OF GOING OUT
WITH HER-- NEVER!
REALLY?
YEAH, BUT AFTER
YOU SAID IT WAS OKAY,
I FIGURED, WHY NOT?
OH, SO...
SO, NOT REALLY NEVER?
I HAVE TO SAY
YOU ARE A MUCH BIGGER
PERSON THAN I AM.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
I JUST...
I WISH I HAD A BROTHER
TO RECIPROCATE.
OH.
IF YOU EVER WANT
TO GO OUT WITH MONICA
YOU HAVE MY BLESSING.
AND MINE.
CHANDLER?
I THINK I'M SICK.
REALLY?
STRUCK DOWN
IN THE PRIB OF LIBE.
OKAY, FINE, I ADMIT IT.
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
WILL YOU PLEASE
RUB THIS ON MY CHEST?
NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU ARE NOT GETTING ME THIS WAY.
I REALLY NEED YOUR HELP.
NO, NO, NO, NO!
FINE, I'LL JUST
RUB IT ON MYSELF.
OKAY.
SO, YOU'RE JUST...
KIND OF RUBBING IT ON YOURSELF?
YEAH?
IT'S NICE.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
IS THIS TURNING YOU ON?
YES.
WELL, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WHAT IS IT?
IS IT THE RUBBING OR THE SMELL?
IT'S ALL VERY, VERY GOOD.
OH...
SO, YOU WANT TO GO, UH...
MIX IT UP?
NOT NOW, I'M SICK.
OH, COME ON, YOU BIG FAKER!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR RULE
ABOUT NEVER SLEEPING
WITH SICK PEOPLE?
WELL, THAT WAS BEFORE ALL THE...
VAPORIZING ACTION.
OKAY, IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO HAVE SEX.
OKAY!
WORKED LIKE A CHARM.
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
THIS IS WHERE ROSS AND I
ARE MEETING FOR OUR DATE.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, I...
I DON'T LIKE IT.
REALLY?
IT'S KIND OF SLUTTY.
IT'S YOURS.
YEAH, WELL, I'M...
I'M A SLUT.
ME, TOO.
HEY.
HI, JILL.
HI...
RACHEL!
RACHEL.
WELL...
YOU'RE NOT AT HOME.
YOU'RE, YOU'RE RIGHT HERE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I BET YOU THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE WEIRD...
BUT IT'S NOT.
OKAY.
SO, WELL, I'LL, UM...
I'LL HAVE HER
HOME BY MIDNIGHT.
( forced laughter )
( crying )
WHY AREN'T YOU HOME YET?
Monica:
IS SOMEONE THERE?
OH, YEAH, IT'S ME.
SORRY.
Chandler:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UH, I'M JUST...
I'M JUST LOOKING OUT
YOUR WINDOW...
AT THE VIEW.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
WE GOT SOME VAPO-RUB
IN SOME PLACES.
OH!
OH, HE BROUGHT HER
BACK TO HIS APARTMENT.
WHO?
IS THAT YOUR SISTER?
OH, SHE IS A SLUT!
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS IS ON A DATE
WITH YOUR SISTER?
HOW WEIRD IS THAT?
OH, MY GOD, LOOK, LOOK.
HE'S TAKING OFF HER CLOTHES.
HE'S TAKING OFF
HER COAT.
Rachel:
OH, THIS IS JUST TERRIBLE.
OH, NO, IT'S NOT.
IT'S A FIRST DATE.
I'M SURE THAT NOTHING
IS GOING TO...
OH!
OOH-HOO...
HE'S GOING TO GET SOME.
OF THE GLARE...
FROM THE STREETLIGHT...
OUT OF HIS APARTMENT.
YOU KNOW, SO, UM...
HE'S CLOSED THE DRAPES THERE
SO HE CAN HAVE A NICE,
PLEASANT CONVERSATION
WITH YOUR LITTLE SISTER.
WELL, I'M OFF TO BED.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]